Hello everyone, my name is Davinder Verma.
I am here to present ARI retail software.
So, lets get started.
There is no compromise with the quality.
It is A quality retail pos software.
It’s the best software in the industry.
It’s made by web masters.
The software was specially designed for easy
of use and the UI is creates a unique customer
experience.
There are many benefits of using the ARI.
Some of them are as follows:
It attracts more sales due to the amazing
customer experience using our software.
It helps to be ahead the competition and be
on the edge.
It helps to be agile in business.
Nothing is static.
The software gets updated according to the
needs of the time.
It has inventory optimization which helps
to run the business worry free and efficiently.
It’s the one stop solution for the retail
industry.
It collects the customer usage statistics
and targets them most effectively using the
data for more sales.
The software is agile which helps to maintain
the business ideally.
The software includes features such as POS,
Customer Rewards, Inventory management, Supply
chain management and many more.
Use ARI to tackle all the business challenges.
It has integrated POS, inventory optimization
which all results in more sales cause of efficient
functioning of the business.
It has integrations with Xero, Microsoft Dynamics
356, Quick books and many more for the business
needs.
ARI is really secured software, so you don’t
have to worry about being hacked with the
rise in cybercrimes.
We have great customer service which provides
all the knowledge needed to use the software
and is available 24 / 7.
ARI helps you conquer many challenges such
as Loyalty problem, increased competition,
IT security issues and stagnant customer service.
Increase your business competitiveness using
ARI.
The software uses the data gathered on customers
for targeted retail strategies and UI is tailored
by there preferences, so they are attracted
to buy more things as they find it easy here.
The personal touch for everyone creates amazing
experiences which spreads the good things
about the business by word of mouth which
in return grows the business.
Our POS System is fast and secure.
It is highly customizable according to business
needs and is well connected with back office.
It is multilingual which makes it useable
worldwide.
It has multiple payment options for the convenience
of customers.
It also has cash drawer restrictions for safety
of the cash counter.
The intuitive interface makes it easy to use
and generates reports with just a click.
It has tax and discounts option so that you
don’t have to manually do things.
It has user profiles so every user can set
their UI according to their personal preferences.
Why choose ARI?
We have a great customer service for solving
all your problems.
We offer competitive software pricing.
Using our software saves a lot of time and
manpower which in turn saves you money.
It is highly customizable according to your
needs.
It has amazing UI with multiple payment options
for ultimate customer satisfaction.
Rating the product.
1.
You can schedule employees to work at multiple
location, but you cannot categorize employees
by job type.
2.
The ARI retail software is affordable by almost
every business out there.
3.
The web module can run on any device with
web browser.
If you talk about the POS.
It can run on any windows device with windows
7 and above whereas for MACs it can run on
MAC OS X and above.
4.
ARI software is very efficient.
It requires minimum hardware requirement,
which is just 4 GB of ram, 10 GB of storage
and just 2Ghz of clock speed for CPU.
Thank you so much for watching.
I hope you got good understanding of the ARI
software.